Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 7: Negatives, 1964-2004
  - Fitch 4306-4310 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    4309 and 4310 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4311-4315 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 4316-4320 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 4321-4325 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 4326-4330 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 4331-4335 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 4336-4340 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 4341-4345 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 4346-4350 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    4349 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 4351-4355 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    4355 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 4356-4360 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 4361-4365 [negatives], 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    4363 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 4366-4370 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 4371-4375 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 4376-4380 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 4381-4385 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 4386-4390 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 4391-4395 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 4396-4400 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    4400 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4401-4405 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 4406-4410 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    4409-4410 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4411-4415 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    4411-4415 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4416-4420 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    4416-4420 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4421-4425 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    4421, 4423 and 4424 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4426-4430 [negatives], 1975 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 4431-4435 [negatives], 1975-1976 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    4434 and 4435 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4436-4440 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    4436-4438 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4441-4445 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    4444 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4446-4450 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    4450 removed to Series 2: Classics. 4446-4449 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4451-4455 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    4451-4453 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4456-4460 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 4461-4465 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 4466-4470 [negatives], 1976 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Fitch 4471-4475 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 4476-4480 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 4481-4485 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 4486-4490 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 4491-4495 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 4496-4500 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 4501-4505 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 4506-4510 [negatives], 1976 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 4511-4515 [negatives], 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 4516-4520 [negatives], 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 4521-4525 [negatives], 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    4523 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 4526-4530 [negatives], 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 4531-4535 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 4536-4540 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 4541-4545 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 4546-4550 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 4551-4555 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 4556-4560 [negatives], 1977 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 4561-4565 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 4566-4570 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 4571-5475 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    4575-5475 missing.
  - Fitch 5476-5480 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5481-5485 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5486-5490 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5491-5495 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 5496-5500 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 5501-5505 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 5506-5510 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 5511-5515 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 5516-5520 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 5521-5525 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 5526-5530 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 5531-5535 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 5536-5540 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 5541-5545 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 5546-5550 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 5551-5555 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 5556-5560 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 5561-5570 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    5665-5669 missing.
  - Fitch 5571-5575 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 5576-5580 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 5581-5585 [negatives], 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 5586-5590 [negatives], 1978-1979 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 5591-5595 [negatives], 1978-1979 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5596-5600 [negatives], 1978-1979 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5601-5605 [negatives], 1978-1979 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5606-5610 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 5611-5615 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 5616-5620 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 5621-5625 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 5626-5630 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 5631-5635 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 5636-5640 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 5641-5645 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 5646-5650 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 5651-5655 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 5656-5660 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 5661-5665 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 5666-5670 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 5671-5675 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 5676-5680 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 5681-5685 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5686-5690 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5691-5695 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5696-5700 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 5701-5705 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 5706-5710 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 5711-5715 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 5716-5720 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 5721-5725 [negatives], 1979-1989 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 5726-5730 [negatives], 1980-1989 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 5731-5735 [negatives], 1980-1989 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 5736-5740 [negatives], 1980-1989 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 5741-5745 [negatives], 1980-1989 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 5746-5750 [negatives], 1980-1989 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 5751-5755 [negatives], 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 5756-5760 [negatives], 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 5761-5765 [negatives], 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 5766-5770 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 5771-5775 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 5776-5780 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5781 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5782 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5783 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 5784 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 5785 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 5786-5790 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    5788 missing.
  - Fitch 5791-5795 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 5796-5800 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 5801-5805 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 5806-5810 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 5811-5815 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 5816-5820 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 5821-5825 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 5826-5830 [negatives], 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 5831-5835 [negatives], 1993 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 5836-5840 [negatives], 1993 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 5841-5845 [negatives], 1993-1994 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 5846-5850 [negatives], 1994 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 5851-5855 [negatives], 1994 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 5856-5860 [negatives], 1994 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 5861-5865 [negatives], 1994 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    5862 missing.
  - Fitch 5866-5870 [negatives], 1994 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 5871-5875 [negatives], 1995 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5876-5880 [negatives], 1995 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5881-5885 [negatives], 1995 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5886-5890 [negatives], 1995 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 5891-5895 [negatives], 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 5896-5900 [negatives], 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    5900 missing.
  - Fitch 5901-5905 [negatives], 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 5906-5910 [negatives], 1995-1997 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 5911-5915 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 5916-5920 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 5921 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 5922 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 5923 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 5924 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 5925 [negatives], 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 5926-5930 [negatives], 1999 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 5931-5935 [negatives], 1999 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 5936-5940 [negatives], 1999 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 5941-5945 [negatives], 1999 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    5943 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 5946-5950 [negatives], 1999 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 5951-5955 [negatives], 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 5956-5960 [negatives], 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 5961-5965 [negatives], 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 5966-5970 [negatives], 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 24)
    5968 missing. 5966 and 5967 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 5971-5975 [negatives], 1999-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 5976-5980 [negatives], 1999-2001 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 5981-5985 [negatives], 1999-2001 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 5986-5990 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    5990 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 5991-5995 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    5993-5994 missing.
  - Fitch 5996-6000 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    5999 removed to Series 2: Classics. 5996 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6001-6005 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 6006-6010 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 6011-6015 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 6016-6020 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 6021-6025 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 6026-6030 [negatives], 2001 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 6031-6035 [negatives], 2001-2002 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 6036-6040 [negatives], 2001-2002 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 6041-6045 [negatives], 2001-2002 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 6046-6050 [negatives], 2001-2002 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    6046-6048 missing.
  - Fitch 6051-6055 [negatives], 2001-2002 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 6056-6060 [negatives], 2003 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 6061-6065 [negatives], 2003 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 6066-6070 [negatives], 2003 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 6071-6075 [negatives], 2003 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    6072 missing.
  - Fitch 6076-6080 [negatives], 2003 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 6081-6085 [negatives], 2003 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 6086-6090 [negatives], 2003 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 6091-6095 [negatives], 2003 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 6096-6100 [negatives], 2003-2004 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    6097 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6101-6105 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 6106-6110 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    6108-6110 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6111-6115 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    6111 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6116-6120 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 6121-6125 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 6126-6130 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    6127 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6131-6135 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 6136-6140 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 6141-6145 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 6146-6150 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 6151-6155 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 6156-6160 [negatives], 2004 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 6161-6165 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 6166-6170 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 6171-6175 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 6176-6180 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 6181-6185 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 6186-6190 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    6190 removed to restricted box.
  - Fitch 6191-6195 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 6196-6200 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 6201-6205 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 6206-6210 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 6211-6215 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 6216-6220 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 6221-6225 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 6226-6230 [negatives], 2004 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    6230 removed to restricted box.
- Series 8: Business Records, 1964-2016
  Contains mostly contracts, licensing agreements and permissions for the use of Bob Fitch photographs. Additionally there is a small amount of research materials, brochures, correspondence, indexes and lists.
  - Business Records: Black Star Agency contracts, 1982-2003 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Business Records: Contracts [part 1 of 2], 1990-2002 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Business Records: Contracts [part 2 of 2], 1990-2002 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2003 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2003-2004 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2006-2007 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2006-2009 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Business Records: Contracts [part 1 of 2], 2006-2012 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Business Records: Contracts [part 2 of 2], 2006-2012 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2010-2014 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2014 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Business Records: Contracts, 2015-2016 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Business Records: Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial statue in Washington, D.C., 2007 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Business Records: Salt Lake City exhibit, 2013 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Business Records: Dorothy Day film, 2006-2007 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Business Records: Photo permissions, 1964-1973 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Photographs on CD and United Farm Workers index, 2000-2016 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Backup images on CDs, 2000-2016 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Printed index for images on computer, 2000-2016 (Box 126, Folder 10)
- Series 9: Computer Media/Digital Materials, 2004-2016
  This series consists of documents, graphics, spreadsheets, databases, software programs, video, audio, and other material created and/or stored on computers, removable media, and hard drives managed by Bob Fitch. The digital files are forensically captured from images of those stored on hard drives, floppy diskettes, CD-ROMs and other media in the Bob Fitch Photography Archive. A portion of the files in this series are digitized copies of Bob Fitch’s photographs. Bob Fitch created 35 galleries of digital images and transferred these galleries to Stanford University Libraries to be viewable online. These are images that Fitch selected and reformatted digitally, as well as images created using a digital camera. Most of the galleries can be viewed through this link: https://exhibits.stanford.edu/fitch
  There are two additional galleries: Nonviolent Peaceforce in Sri Lanka, 2005 https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/hh188hp7947
  Marches, Demonstrations, Social Justice, 1964-2011 https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/nb583sk7324
  NOTE Computer media are housed in Boxes 138 - 139.